Finding Aid for the Yvar Mikhashoff Photograph Collection, circa 1930-1993
State University of New York at Buffalo. Music Library
- Photographs and drawings of Yvar Mikhashoff alone, 1950-1993, I.; Containers 1-2, 5 drawings, 133 photographs
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in dark jacket standing next to a wall with the ship Queen Elizabeth 2 in the background, August 1993, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item YM02-068)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in dark jacket standing next to a wall with the ship Queen Elizabeth 2 in the background, August 1993, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item YM02-069)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in dark jacket standing next to a wall with the ship Queen Elizabeth 2 in the background, August 1993, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item YM02-070)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in dark jacket standing next to a wall with the ship Queen Elizabeth 2 in the background, August 1993, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item YM02-071)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in dark jacket standing next to a wall with the ship Queen Elizabeth 2 in the background, August 1993, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item YM02-072)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in dark jacket standing next to a wall with the ship Queen Elizabeth 2 in the background, August 1993, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item YM02-073)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in white shirt, holding ornate umbrella, standing on stairs of temple, August 1993, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item YM02-074)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in white shirt, holding ornate umbrella, standing on stairs of temple, August 1993, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item YM02-075)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in white shirt, holding ornate umbrella, sitting on stairs of temple, August 1993, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item YM02-076)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in red bath robe playing piano in his house in Buffalo, August 1993, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 2, Item YM02-077)
- Photographs of Yvar Mikhashoff with other people, other people without Mikhashoff, Mikhashoff alone when part of a photographic sequence, and scenes from Mikhashoff's travels, circa 1930-circa 1990, II.; Containers 3-4, 285 photographs
  - Aaron Copland, 1930, 1 black and white photograph; Van Vechten, Carl, 1880-1964 (Box 3, Item YM03-001)
  - John Cage, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-002)
  - Milton Babbitt in electronic music studio, hand-colored photograph, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-003)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in white shirt and tie, seated with doublebass in background, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-004)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in white shirt and tie, seated at table with unidentified man, doublebass in background, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-005)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff with "Bernd", 1963-64, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-006)
  - Two costumed women with man in clown costume, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-007)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing on a bridge over a river in Czechoslovakia, 1968-10, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-008)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing on staircase with rotunda in background, 1968-10, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-009)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing in front of stone building in Czechoslovakia, 1968-10, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-010)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing in front of flower bed in Czechoslovakia, 1968-10, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-011)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing on balcony of building in Czechoslovakia, 1968-10, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-012)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing across street from Hotel Eden in Czechoslovakia, 1968-10, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-013)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing in front of flower bed and building in Czechoslovakia, 1968-10, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-014)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff with John Costa (left) and Erastus Corning, March 1971, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-015)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff with John Costa (left) and Erastus Corning, March 1971, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-016)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff with friends in lobby of the Palace Theater, Albany, N.Y., March 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-017)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff with friends in lobby of the Palace Theater, Albany, N.Y., March 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-018)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff with friends in lobby of the Palace Theater, Albany, N.Y., March 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-019)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing at the piano onstage with the Albany Symphony Orchestra, March 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-020)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing at the piano onstage with the Albany Symphony Orchestra, March 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-021)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in formal dress in green room at Palace Theater, Albany, N.Y., March 1971, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-022)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in formal dress in the Albany Institute of History and Art, 1973-03-11, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-023)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in formal dress in the Albany Institute of History and Art, March 11 1973, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-024)
  - Topper Mackay (brother of Yvar Mikhashoff) playing guitar, seated next to his wife (white turtleneck), March 1973, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-025)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in formal attire, with unidentified man in Albany Institute of History and Art, March 11 1973, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-026)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff at the piano at the Albany Institute of History and Art, March 11 1973, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-027)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff at the piano with Isabelle Ganz, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-028)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff at the piano with Isabelle Ganz and Benjamin Hudson, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-029)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff at the piano with Isabelle Ganz and Benjamin Hudson, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-030)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff at piano with Barbara Bond, soprano, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-031)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff and unidentified male at restaurant table, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-032)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff at the piano with unidentified male page turner, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Melvin, Glenn (Box 3, Item YM03-033)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff (right) with two unidentified males, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-034)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff taking a bow on stage, 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-035)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff at the piano onstage with Isabelle Ganz and Joseph Rothstein, 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-036)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff at the piano onstage with Isabelle Ganz and Joseph Rothstein, 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-037)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff and Candice Channing, 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-038)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff at the piano with Isabelle Ganz, Candice Channing, and Joseph Rothstein, 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-039)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff, Isabelle Ganz, Candice Channing, and Joseph Rothstein taking a bow, 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-040)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff, Isabelle Ganz, and Joseph Rothstein, 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-041)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff, Isabelle Ganz, Candice Channing, and Joseph Rothstein taking bow, 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-042)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff, Isabelle Ganz, Candice Channing, and Joseph Rothstein posed shots, contact sheet, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-043)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff, Isabelle Ganz, Joseph Rothstein, and Candice Channing, 1974, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-044)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff, Isabelle Ganz, Joseph Rothstein, and Candice Channing, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-045)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff, Isabelle Ganz, Candice Channing, and Joseph Rothstein, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-046)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in red shirt conducting at piano, with Amy Winn, flute, Wayne Crouse, viola, Isabelle Ganz, vocalist, and Ira Black, at lectern, March 1974, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-047)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in red shirt conducting at piano, with Amy Winn, flute, Wayne Crouse, viola, Isabelle Ganz, vocalist, and Ira Black, at lectern, March 1974, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-048)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in red shirt taking bow, onstage with Amy Winn, flute, Isabelle Ganz, vocalist, Wayne Crouse, viola, Richard Brown (partial), and Ira Black, at far left, March 1974, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-049)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in red shirt taking bow with Ira Black, Amy Winn, flute, Isabelle Ganz, vocalist, Wayne Crouse, viola, and Richard Brown, percussion, March 1974, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-050)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in dark jacket at the piano with Isabelle Ganz, vocalist and Wayne Crouse, viola, March 1974, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-051)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in dark jacket taking bow with Isabelle Ganz, vocalist and Wayne Crouse, viola, March 1974, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-052)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in dark jacket at the piano with Amy Winn, flute, March 1974, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-053)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in dark jacket and tie taking bow with Amy Winn, flute, and Wayne Crouse, viola, March 1974, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-054)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff at piano onstage with Isabelle Ganz, vocalist, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-055)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff at piano on darkened stage, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-056)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff at piano onstage with Benjamin Hudson, violin, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-057)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff at piano onstage with Benjamin Hudson, violin, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-058)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in white suit at piano, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-059)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in dark jacket and light trousers playing clusters at piano, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-060)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in white suit at piano onstage with unidentified female vocalist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-061)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in white suit taking bow with unidentified female vocalist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-062)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in white jacket onstage with Heinz Rehfuss, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-063)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in white jacket taking bow with Heinz Rehfuss, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-064)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in dark jacket taking bow with unidentified female vocalist, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-065)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in formal dress at table with four unidentified people, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-066)
  - Heinz Rehfuss and Carlo Pinto, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-067)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff, Heinz Rehfuss, and Carlo Pinto, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-068)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in white jacket (right) with Suze Leal Rehfuss and unidentified male, undated, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-069)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff with Nils Vigeland (left) and brother, Topper Mackay (right) and unidentified male, 1976, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-070)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff playing piano in Israeli home, 1977, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-071)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff playing piano in Israeli home, Isabelle Ganz singing, 1977, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-072)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff playing piano in Israeli home, Isabelle Ganz singing, 1977, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-073)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff with Isabelle Ganz in Israel, 1977, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-074)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff with Isabelle Ganz in Israel, 1977, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-075)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff by road sign in Israel, 1977, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-076)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff with camel in Israel, 1977, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-077)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff with camel in Israel, 1977, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-078)
  - Isabelle Ganz with camel in Israel, 1977, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-079)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in headress in Israel, 1977, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-080)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in headress in Israel playing folk flute, 1977, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-081)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in headress in Israel playing folk flute, 1977, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-082)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff and Frances-Marie Uitti, violoncello, 1977-04-23, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-083)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff and Frances-Marie Uitti taking bow, 1977-04-23, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-084)
  - Frances-Marie Uitti, 1977-06, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-085)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in white suit with Frances-Marie Uitti, 1977-06, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-086)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in white suit with Frances-Marie Uitti, 1977-06, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-087)
  - Paul Schmidt? in straw hat seated in wicker chair, June 22 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-088)
  - Paul Schmidt? and Joan Collopy, June 22 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-089)
  - Paul Schmidt? and Joan Collopy, June 22 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-090)
  - Paul Schmidt? And Joan Collopy, June 22 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-091)
  - Contact sheet with images of Paul Schmidt, Joan Collopy, William Kirkpatrick (dancer), Yvar Mikhashoff, Frances-Marie Uitti, Benjamin Hudson, and Gary Hatt, June 22 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-092)
  - Contact sheet with images of Paul Schmidt, Joan Collopy, William Kirkpatrick (dancer), Yvar Mikhashoff, Frances-Marie Uitti, and Ralph Jones (22a), June 22 1977, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-093)
  - Contact sheet with images of Paul Schmidt, Joan Collopy, Yvar Mikhashoff, and Frances-Marie Uitti, June 22 1977, 1 black and white contact sheet; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-094)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in blue shirt at piano and Frances-Marie Uitti, violoncello, January 10 1978, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-095)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in dark jacket at piano and Frances-Marie Uitti, violoncello, June 30 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Riemens, Wim (Box 3, Item YM03-096)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff and Frances-Marie Uitti, June 30 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Riemens, Wim (Box 3, Item YM03-097)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff performing at piano (right hand raised), Frances-Marie Uitti, violoncello, and unidentified female violinist, June 30 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Riemens, Wim (Box 3, Item YM03-098)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff performing at piano, Frances-Marie Uitti, violoncello, and unidentified female violinist, June 30 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Riemens, Wim (Box 3, Item YM03-099)
  - William Kirkpatrick, dancer, November 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 3, Item YM03-100)
  - William Kirkpatrick, dancer, onstage in front of projected image of a page from Sylvano Bussotti score, November 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 3, Item YM03-101)
  - William Kirkpatrick, dancer, onstage in front of projected image of a page from Sylvano Bussotti score, November 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 3, Item YM03-102)
  - William Kirkpatrick, dancer, onstage in front of projected image of a page from Sylvano Bussotti score, November 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 3, Item YM03-103)
  - William Kirkpatrick, dancer, kneeling on piano strings, Yvar Mikhashoff at keyboard, November 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 3, Item YM03-104)
  - William Kirkpatrick, dancer, onstage in front of projected image of a page from Sylvano Bussotti score, November 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 3, Item YM03-105)
  - William Kirkpatrick, dancer, onstage in front of projected image of a page from Sylvano Bussotti score, November 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 3, Item YM03-106)
  - William Kirkpatrick, dancer, onstage with beanbag cushion, November 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 3, Item YM03-107)
  - William Kirkpatrick, dancer, onstage with beanbag cushion, November 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 3, Item YM03-108)
  - William Kirkpatrick, dancer, onstage with beanbag cushion, November 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 3, Item YM03-109)
  - William Kirkpatrick, dancer, onstage with beanbag cushion, November 1978, 1 black and white photograph; Haupt, Irene (Box 3, Item YM03-110)
  - Camel in foreground with the Sphinx and Pyramid in background, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-111)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing with Great Pyramid in background, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-112)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff on horse with Great Pyramid in background, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-113)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff on horse with Great Pyramid in background, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-114)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in red sweater standing in Egyptian landscape, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-115)
  - Entanceway to structure in Jordan, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-116)
  - Horses with cliff dwellings of Petra, Jordan in background, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-117)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff, on horse, with guide in Jordan, cliff dwellings of Petra in background, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-118)
  - Brass ensemble playing outside Karlstejn Castle, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-119)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff with two unidentified friends in Czechoslovakia, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-120)
  - Karlstejn Castle, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-121)
  - Karlstejn Castle, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-122)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in red swaeter in Israel or Jordan, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-123)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in red jacket on stone beach in Israel or Jordan, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-124)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in red jacket seated on beach chair in Israel, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-125)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in red jacket standing on beach in Israel, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-126)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff on the stairs of the Temple of the Magician, Uxmal, Mexico, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-127)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff on the stairs of the Temple of the Magician, Uxmal, Mexico, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-128)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing before ruins at Uxmal, Mexico, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-129)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing in front of temple at Teotihuacán, Mexico, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-130)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff sitting at Tulum archeological site, Mexico, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-131)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff at table in Hotel Genève, Mexico City, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-132)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing outside, possibly in Mexico City, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-133)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff closeup, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-134)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing on beach between two buildings in San Pedro (Belize?), undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-135)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in formal dress dancing with unidentified woman in white turban and boa, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-136)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in formal dress dancing with unidentified woman in white turban and boa, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-137)
  - Leo Smit and unidentified woman in white turban and boa, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-138)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff with blue bow tie, with unidentified friends, 1979, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-139)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in red jacket and red tie with unidentified friends, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-140)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff in red jacket seated at piano, undated, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-141)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff at piano, with Benjamin Hudson, violin and Wayne Crouse, viola, 1979-04, 1 color photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-142)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing in front of piano at Schiller College (location not specified), 1980-03-08, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-143)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff taking bow at Schiller College (location not specified), 1980-03-08, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-144)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff seated at piano at Schiller College (location not specified), March 8 1980, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-145)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff seated at piano, addressing audience at Schiller College (location not specified), March 8 1980, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-146)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff seated at piano, addressing audience at Schiller College (location not specified), March 8 1980, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-147)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff standing in front of piano at Schiller College (location not specified), March 8 1980, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-148)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff performing at piano at Schiller College (location not specified), March 8 1980, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-149)
  - Yvar Mikhashoff performing at piano at Schiller College (location not specified), March 8 1980, 1 black and white photograph; Unidentified (Box 3, Item YM03-150)